



















Ahmed Zafar · 2nd

DevOps | Automation | Cloud Infrastructure | Linux | OSS



Sydney, New South Wales, Australia · Contact info

500+ connections



Ali Habibi, Premalatha Padmanabbhan, and 2 other mutual connections

Connect





About

Experienced Consultant with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Strong consulting professional skilled in DevOps, Automation and Linux.

Activity

637 followers

Ahmed hasn't posted lately

Ahmed's recent posts and comments will be displayed here.

Show all activity →

Experience



OSS Consultant

Mar 2011 - Jun 2018 · 7 yrs 4 mos

Riyadh, Saudi Arabia



OBS Engineer

Nokia Siemens Networks

Mar 2005 - Mar 2011 · 6 yrs 1 mo



Project Engineer

Siemens

Mar 2005 - Mar 2007 · 2 yrs 1 mo

Education



Curtin University

2000 - 2004

Licenses & certifications



Ericsson Certified Associate - Ericsson Cloud

Ericsson

Issued Oct 2015

Show credential 2



AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Issued Feb 2017 · Expired Feb 2020

Show credential 🗷

Skills

NSN

Amazon Web Services (AWS)



Passed LinkedIn Skill Assessment

Technical Support

Show all 42 skills →

Recommendations

Received

Given



Kumar G. · 2nd

System Engineer - Kubernetes | Docker| AWS| Linux at Commonwealth Bank July 21, 2018, Kumar worked with Ahmed on the same team

Ahmed is a wonderful guy and great colleague, to work with. He is perfect team player anybody wish for. His knowledge of Network Management System like Anritsu Masterclaw, Ericsson OSS, Ericsson So-Em is appreciable. If i will ever get a chance, I will love to work with him again.



Ismail Fareed · 2nd

Leadership, Program/Project Management(PMP), BSS & Fintech, Charging, Cloud, 5G, IT and Technology Enthusiast

June 26, 2018, Ismail managed Ahmed directly

Ahmed is one of the hardworking and dedicated individuals I have worked with. He worked under my supervision in Ericsson Saudi and he is very self reliant and capable of handling assigned tasks in a very professional manner and always willing to accept new challenges. He would make an asset to a...



Saleh Fayyad · 2nd

Engineering Manager - Network Performance at Mobily June 19, 2018, Saleh was Ahmed's client

I worked with Ahmad as part of my daily job in Mobily, he is very professional person, enjoys talented skills not only to handle daily tasks but also to create innovative ways to enhance the quality of job done like scripting and automation ...

Show all 13 received →

Interests

Companies

Groups Schools



1,522,399 followers

+ Follow



Nextgen Group

6.268 followers



Show all 37 companies →



Start improving your content with Content
Optimizer today





Get better results with more engaging emails

Sign Up

People also viewed



Aaron Gorka · 3rd

DevOps | Cloud | Docker | Serverless | Python

+ Connect



Haider Ali · 2nd

Cloud | Linux | System Engineering | Technical Support | Leadership

-+ Connect



Mohsin Haqqani · 3rd

OSS Solution Architect / OSS Specialist

♠ Message



Brian Meyers · 3rd

Devops Engineer at amaysim Australia Ltd

-+ Connect



Shaun Gorman · 2nd

Infrastructure Engineer of AWS, Windows, VMWare and Linux

-+ Connect

Show more ✓

People you may know



Shaikh Muhammad Faizan

Deputy Manager Software Development

- Connect



Arun Kumar J

Project Engineer at Specialized & Interactive Systems

- Connect



Amir Abbas

Project Engineer at INTEREL

+ Connect



Danish Khan

Channel Sales Manager at Microsoft

- Connect

